α	Alpha-Zerfall (Emission eines Heliumatomkerns) 
β−	Beta−-Zerfall (Emission eines Elektrons) 
β+	Beta+-Zerfall (Emission eines Positrons) 
ββ	Doppelter Betazerfall (gleichzeitige Emission zweier Elektronen) 
K	Einfang eines Elektrons der inneren Elektronenhülle 
KEC	Doppelter Elektroneneinfang 
IT	Isomerer Übergang 
SF	Spontanspaltung 
p	erfall unter Emission eines Protons 
n	Zerfall unter Emission eines Neutrons 
Xy	Cluster-Zerfall unter Emission eines Kerns Xy 


Decay Mode:
Decay modes are given in decreasing strength
from left to right, followed by the percentage
branching, if known ("w" indicates a weak
branch). The percentage branching is omitted
where there is no competing mode of decay or
no other mode has been observed. A "?" indicates
an expected but not observed mode of decay[5].
The various modes of decay are given below:

β–		β– decay
ε		ε (electron capture), or ε+β+, or β+ decay
IT		isomeric transition (through γ or conversion–electron decay)
n, p, α, . . .	neutron, proton, alpha, ... decay
SF		spontaneous fission
2β–, 3α, . . .	double β– decay (β–β–) , decay through emission of 3 α' s , . . .
β–n, β–p, 		delayed n, p, α, . . .
β–α, . . .		(emission following β–decay)
εp, εα,		delayed p, α, SF, ...
εSF, ...		(emission following ε or β+ decay)